<Document>
  # I.P.C.
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobIPCDummy" Caption="I.P.C."/>
  An IPC (short for Integrated Positronic Chassis) is a type of sentient robot and is considered an [color=yellow]independent individual[/color], meaning [color=red]they are not guided by any laws of robotics[/color]. IPCs cannot be hacked by Emags because they do not have to follow any predefined directives in their system. [color=red]IPCs are silicon-based beings, so doctors do not have the skills to repair them.[/color]

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PositronicBrain" Caption="Positronic Brain"/>
  </Box>
  Like borgs, IPCs have a positronic brain as their processing source. However, unlike them, IPCs can't be assembled. "It's cheaper to create a shell that obeys you than one that doesn't! *wink*"

  ## Recharging an IPC
   <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic" Caption="APC Terminal"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BorgCharger" Caption="Borg Charger"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PowerCellMedium" Caption="Power Cell"/>
  </Box>
  IPCs can be recharged in three different ways:

  APC Terminal: IPCs can use APC terminals to recharge. Press [color=yellow]Alt + left click[/color] on a terminal as many times as needed to fully recharge.

  Borg Rechargers: IPCs can use borg rechargers to recharge. Always prioritize the ones outside of the Sci area to avoid headaches.

  Power Cell: IPCs have an internal power cell that serves as their battery. They can simply swap it out by opening the hatch and manually replacing it.

  ## Integrated Radio
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EncryptionKeyScience" Caption="Encryption key"/>
  </Box>

  КПБ не [bold]могут[/bold] использовать внешние радиоприемники, потому что в них уже есть встроенный модуль. Им нужно только получить ключ шифрования от радиоприемника. Щелкнув по КПБ с помощью [color=желтый] кусачки[/color], вы можете удалить их ключи.
  Вы можете найти новые клавиши по всей станции или вынуть одну из них из секторного радиоприемника с помощью [color=yellow] отвёртки[/color].

  ## Ремонт
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WelderIndustrialAdvanced" Caption="Welder"/>
    Сварочные аппараты можно использовать для устранения [color=yellow] грубых[/color] повреждений.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CableApcStack" Caption="Cables (any type)"/>
    Кабели можно использовать для устранения [color=желтый] ожогов[/color].
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetGlass" Caption="Glass Sheets (any type)"/>
   Стеклянные листы можно использовать для устранения [color=yellow] слепоты[/color].
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
<<<<<<< HEAD:Resources/ServerInfo/Guidebook/Mobs/IPC.xml
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="N14MaterialCircuitry10" Caption="Circuitry"/>
    Circuitry can be used to repair [color=yellow]Brute[/color], [color=yellow]Burns[/color], and [color=yellow]Radiation[/color] damage.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    In the event an IPC dies, after being fully repaired, it should be restarted using the [color=yellow]"Restart"[/color] button (located by right-clicking).
=======
    В случае выхода из строя КПБ после полного восстановления его следует перезапустить с помощью кнопки [color=yellow] "Перезапустить"[/color] (которую можно щелкнуть правой кнопкой мыши).
>>>>>>> c9d8431a6e (Перевод рас в guidebook):Resources/ServerInfo/Guidebook/Mobs/IPCs.xml

    [color=красный]НИКОГДА НЕ ПЫТАЙТЕ КПБ электрическим током с помощью дефибриллятора или каким-либо другим способом, пока он не заряжен, так как это приведет к выбросу энергии из аккумулятора наружу![/color]
  </Box>

</Document>
